<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ponzela Design</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Ponzela Design</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Bipart</title><link>/projects/2023-05-02-bipart/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/2023-05-02-bipart/</guid><description>Bipart is a branding that has been developed for a startup with the objective of providing a practical, objective, and innovative solution for the artists and freelancers in Madrid.</description></item><item><title>Dafne glass</title><link>/projects/2023-05-02-dafne-glass/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/2023-05-02-dafne-glass/</guid><description>The objective of this project, which was initiated for the Bombay Sapphire Cup contest, involved conducting thorough aesthetic research to enhance the safety of the cups.</description></item><item><title>Epizon game</title><link>/projects/2023-05-02-epizon-game/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/2023-05-02-epizon-game/</guid><description>For this project we analyzed various board and card games to create a playful design. Drawing inspiration from classical Greece we ensured that the game was as dynamic and aesthetically pleasing as possible.</description></item><item><title>Headphones</title><link>/projects/2023-05-01-headphones/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/2023-05-01-headphones/</guid><description>This project aims to find and adapt a mechanism, specifically an expandable pulley, that amplifies the coverage of the headphones, thereby enabling more effective sound control.</description></item><item><title>Medical city</title><link>/projects/2023-05-02-medical-city/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/2023-05-02-medical-city/</guid><description>This project aims to create an emblem for the new healthcare city in Jaén, which fosters provincial unity and instills pride among healthcare professionals while providing reassurance to patients.</description></item><item><title>Sitaid</title><link>/projects/2023-05-01-sitaid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/2023-05-01-sitaid/</guid><description>The project involves creating an identity for a product designed to enhance the independence of individuals with motor disabilities by aiding them in getting in and out of vehicles easily.</description></item><item><title/><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>When submitting a job offer, please include the following information to ensure that your offer is considered
Guidelines for job offers Name of the company: Please provide the full name of the company offering the job.
Job position and responsibilities: Clearly state the job title and list the specific responsibilities that come with the role.
Salary range: It is important to include the salary range that corresponds to the position being offered.</description></item></channel></rss>